<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Temukan Tempat</string>
    <string name="splashscreen">Splash Screen</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="me">You</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="andabelumlogin">Anda belum login, silahkan Login terlebih dahulu</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="registrasi">Registrasi</string>
    <string name="copyright">copyright - aladziviesoft.com</string>
    <string name="keterangan">Aplikasi Temukan Tempat ini kami bangun dengan harapan bisa membantu <i><b>SobatPlace</b></i> sekalian untuk menemukan tempat yang ingin cari secara rinci, beda dengan Google Maps, aplikasi ini lebih spesifik dalam tempat. Jadi apa yang menjadi kebutuhan hari hari <i><b>SobatPlace</b></i> sekalian bisa terbantu dalam mencari tempat yang dibutuhkan.</string>
    <string name="namatempat">Nama Tempat</string>
    <string name="latitude">Latitude</string>
    <string name="Longitude">Longitude</string>
    <string name="keteranganTempat">Keterangan</string>
    <string name="jambuka">Jam Buka</string>
    <string name="jamtutup">Jam Tutup</string>
    <string name="fotolokasi">Foto Lokasi</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="take">Take Image</string>
    <string name="simpan">Simpan</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate :</string>
    <string name="deskripsi">Deskripsi Tempat</string>
    <string name="textcontoh">Raja Ampat archipelago is known as a standout amongst the most excellent jumping place on the planet due to the magnificence of its submerged life. The archipelago, which is situated in West Papua, has 610 islands encompassed by enormously clear waters and occupied by a quarter of marine creature species that exist on the planet.  In light of its excellence, this spot turns into a shelter for nautical tourism beaus furthermore as a goliath whale shark environment. Besides, it has a manta point jump that is, a spot for jumpers to swim with titan manta beam that its wings achieves 9 meters in length. We can likewise discover wrecks and airplane from World War II utilized as a living space of elaborate fish and bright anemones.</string>
    <string name="pergi">Pergi ke tempat ini</string>
</resources>
